Daniel Yankelovich Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Projects,1949-1994
  - Subseries C: Work Projects, undated, 1958-1990
    - Related Material
      - Papers
        - Gyllenhammar, P. G., "Needed: Policy to Match Employment With New Technology", undated (Box 54:1285)
        - Hopkins, D. and LaMarre, S., "The Work Ethic of the New Lifestyle Graduate", 1982 (Box 54:1286)
        - Lodge, George C., "The Uses of Ideology for Managers", 1981 (Box 54:1287)
        - Maccoby, M. and K. Terzi, "What Happened to the Work Ethic, 1979 Sep (Box 54:1288)
        - Rosow, J., "Quality of Working Life: An Unchartered Road for Labor", 1981 (Box 55:1289)
        - Salzburg, M., "Working Past Retirement: Practical and Motivational Issues", 1983 May (Box 55:1290-1291)
        - Schmookler, A., "Japan's Economic Success: Its Sources and Its Implications for the United States", 1981 Nov (Box 55:1292)
        - Walton, R. E., "The Topeka Work System: Optimistic Vision, Pessimistic Hypotheses, and Reality", 1981 Nov (Box 55:1293)
        - Yuchtman-Yarr, E. and A. Gottlieb, "Technological Development and the Meaning of Work: A Socio-psychological Perspective", 11873 Oct (Box 55:1294)
      - Social Security, 1984 (Box 55:1295)
      - "Strategic Planning for Human Resources: 1981 and Beyond" - briefing for executives, 1981 (Box 55:1296-1299)
      - White Collar Productivity Improvement project, 1983-1985 (Box 55:1300)
  - Subseries D: Youth Projects, undated, 1965-1980
    - Notes
      - General, [1970] (Box 55:1301-1303)
      - Notecards, [1970] (Box 55:1304)
      - Notes: social trends, [1970] (Box 55:1305)
      - Reading notes: A Culture of Commitment by M. Mead, [1970] (Box 55:1306)
    - "Generations Apart" - a study of the generation gap conducted for CBS News by Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., 1969 (Box 55:1307)
    - Book
      - Outline, [1970] (Box 55:1308)
      - Part I, "Introduction and the Three Revolutions": notes, [1970] (Box 55:1309)
      - Part II, "Misconceptions": notes, [1970] (Box 55:1310)
      - Part III, "Nature of the Phenomenon": notes, [1970] (Box 55:1311)
      - Part IV, "The Great Idea": notes, [1970] (Box 55:1312)
      - Depth interviews and biographies, [1970] (Box 55:1313)
      - Publisher information, 1970 (Box 55:1314)
    - Presentations
      - Handwritten draft, [1965] (Box 55:1315)
      - Presentation to Coca-Cola executives: notes, 1970 May 17 (Box 55:1316)
      - Handwritten draft/notes, "Youth and Social Change", 1970 Jun 10 (Box 55:1317)
      - "Revolution, Reform or Disillusion": notes, 1970 (Box 55:1318)
    - "The Wrong Enemy"
      - Typescript draft, edited, [1970] (Box 55:1319)
      - Chart drafts, [1970] (Box 55:1320)
      - Miscellaneous corrected pages and notes, [1970] (Box 55:1321)
    - "American Youth Today," Draft A, charts and notes, [1965] (Box 56:1322)
    - "Preserving Continuity in Youth Research": memorandum, 1971 Feb 16 (Box 56:1323)
    - "Major Themes of the National Study of the Attitudes of American Youth (14-24) Towards American Foreign Policy": memorandum, 1971 Feb 23 (Box 56:1324)
    - Update on Youth survey form, 1970 (Box 56:1325)
    - Summary of responses to survey on youth and the establishment, 1971 Dec (Box 56:1326)
    - "Some Tentative Hypotheses About Teen-Agers", undated (Box 56:1327)
    - "Appendix B - How the Segments were Evolved", undated (Box 56:1328)
    - "The 1973 Study of American Youth": computer tables, vol. B, by Daniel Yankelovich, Inc., 1973 (Box 56:1329-1331)
    - Draft proposal for 1979 youth study, undated (Box 56:1332)
    - Miscellaneous, undated, 1971 (Box 56:1333)
    - Related Material
      - Satin, A., M. King and G. Richardson, The American Freshman: National Norms for Fall 1977, [1978] (Box 56:1334)
      - Barzun, J. and H. Boardman, "Seminar: Central Influences on American Life", [1971] (Box 56:1335)
      - Brewster, K., speech before the American Council on Education, 1965 Oct 8 (Box 56:1336)
      - Clippings, 1970-1971, 1978 (Box 56:1337)
      - Committee for the Study of National Service, Youth and the Needs of the Nation, 1979 (Box 56:1338)
      - Federations of Americans Supporting Science, "Technology the Economy, and the Space Program", 1973 (Box 56:1339)
      - Hayakawa, S. I., statement before the President's Commission on Student Unrest, 1970 Jul 15 (Box 56:1340)
      - Institute of Life Insurance,, Finance-Related Attitudes of Youth, 1970, 1970 (Box 56:1341)
      - Institute of Life Insurance,, Youth 1974 - Finance-Related Attitudes, 1974 (Box 56:1342)
      - The Internationalist, no. 3, 1971 May/Aug (Box 56:1343)
      - Maxwell, P. and J. Hollomon, "Detailed Notes For a Campaign in Colleges", 1971 Oct (Box 56:1344)
      - Maxwell, P. and J. Hollomon, "Students for Development Project", 1971 Oct (Box 56:1345)
      - Miscellaneous youth material, 1970 (Box 56:1346)
      - "National Service - Moving the Idea Forward" - conference, 1970 Sep (Box 56:1347)
      - Newsletter, 1970 (Box 56:1348)
      - Psychology Today, 1969 Oct (Box 56:1349)
      - "The Role of Youth" - chapter 4, 1972 Sep (Box 56:1350)
      - "The Young Adult in the Age of Complexity", undated (Box 56:1351)
- Series III: Organizations/Professional Services,1960-1992
  - The American Assembly
    - Forty-Third American Assembly meeting, 1973 (Box 57:1352)
    - Introduction to Assembly book, The Changing World of Work, 1973 (Box 57:1353)
    - Assembly convention programs, 1988-1991 (Box 57:1354-1355)
    - Correspondence concerning book edited by Yankelovich, Domestic Foundations: Building U.S. Constituencies for International Engagement After the Cold War, 1992 (Box 57:1356-1357)
    - Eighty-First American Assembly meeting: "After the Soviet Union: Implications for U.S. Policy", 1992 (Box 57:1358)
    - Correspondence concerning book edited by Yankelovich, Americans in a New World: Getting Things Right on the Home Front, 1991-1992 (Box 57:1359-1361)
    - Eighty-Third American Assembly meeting: "Public Engagement in U.S. Foreign Policy After the Cold War", 1993 (Box 57:1362)
    - Correspondence concerning book edited by Yankelovich, Public Support for Foreign Policy After the Cold War, 1991-1992 (Box 57:1363)
    - Notes for Public Support book, 1993 (Box 57:1364)
    - General correspondence, 1993 (Box 57:1365-1366)
  - Aspen Institute Distinguished Fellows, 1989-1990 (Box 57:1367)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies: reports and papers, 1976-1981 (Box 57:1368-1369)
  - Busines-Higher Education Forum meetings, 1991 (Box 57:1370-1371)
  - The Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching
    - Board of Trustees meeting: agenda book, 1988 May 2 (Box 57:1372)
    - Board of Trustees meeting: agenda book, 1991 Apr 23 (Box 58:1373-1374)
    - Board of Trustees meeting: agenda book, 1991 Nov 18 (Box 58:1375-1376)
    - Board of Trustees meeting: agenda book, 1992 Apr 21 (Box 58:1377-1378)
    - Reports
      - Campus Life: In Search of Community: news clippings, 1990 (Box 58:1379)
      - A Classification of Institutions of Higher Education, 1987 (Box 58:1380)
      - The Condition of Teaching, A State by State Analysis, 1990, 1990 (Box 58:1381)
      - An Imperiled Generation: Saving Urban Schools, 1988 (Box 58:1382)
      - An Imperiled Generation: Saving Urban Schools: news clippings, 1988 (Box 58:1383-1384)
      - Ready to Learn: A Mandate for the Nation: draft, 1991 (Box 58:1385-1386)
      - Ready to Learn: A Mandate for the Nation, 1991 (Box 59:1387-1388)
  - The Center for American Culture Studies, Columbia University, 1991 (Box 59:1389)
  - Changing Domestic Priorities Project Advisory Board
    - Board meeting: agenda book, 1982 Apr 7 (Box 59:1390)
    - Board meeting: agenda book, 1982 Dec 10 (Box 59:1391)
  - Council on Competiveness (and related material)
    - Challenges: Council on Competitiveness newletters, 1989-1991 (Box 59:1392)
    - Perspectives on Productivity: A Global View, 1982 (Box 59:1393)
    - America's Competitive Challenge: The Need for a National Response, 1984 (Box 59:1393)
    - International Trade, Industrial Policies, and the Future of American Industry, 1983 (Box 59:1394)
    - Maintaining Profitability in an Increasingly Complex Environment, 1984 (Box 59:1395)
    - The Need for U.S. Industrial Objectives: A Report of the Industrial Objectives Panel, 1982 (Box 59:1396)
    - Picking Up the Pace: The Commercial Challenge to American Innovation, 1988 (Box 59:1397)
    - America and the Price of Greatness: A Study of the Politics of Investment by Rebuild America - draft, 1988 (Box 59:1398)
    - Global Assessment, no. 3, 1987 Jun (Box 59:1399)
    - A Competitiveness Assessment of the President's FY 1991 Budget, 1991 (Box 59:1400)
    - Competitiveness Index, by Council on Competitiveness, 1989-1990 (Box 59:1401)
    - Legislative and Policy Update: COC newsletters, 1989-1990 (Box 59:1402)
    - Promoting Economic Growth and Competitiveness: Report of the Industrial Policy Study Group, 198 (Box 60:1403)
    - Competitiveness presentation for SIT Investment Associates, 1987-1988 (Box 60:1404-1405)
  - Council on Foreign Relations
    - Presentation concerning council membership survey, [1987] (Box 60:1406)
    - Completed questionnaires, [1987] (Box 60:1407-1408)
    - Council membership survey data reference book, 1987 (Box 60:1409-1411)
    - Council membership survey executive summary, 1987 (Box 60:1412)
    - D. Yankelovich working copy of survey results, [1987] (Box 60:1413-1414)
    - D. Yankelovich survey notes on survey results, 1987 (Box 60:1415-1416)
    - Tabulated breakdown of survey results, 1987 (Box 60:1417-1419)
    - Survey results arranged according to demographic categories, 1987 (Box 60:1420-1422)
    - Survey results arranged according to demographic categories, 1987 (Box 61:1423-1424)
    - Edited D. Yankelovich manuscript on membership survey, 1987 (Box 61:1425)
    - D. Yankelovich summary of membership survey, 1987 (Box 61:1426)
    - Council-sponsored papers, 1987 (Box 61:1427)
      - The Commission on U.S.-Soviet Relations, "The Soviet Challenge: A Policy Framework for the 1980s",1981
      - Marjolin, Robert, "Europe in Search of Its Identity", 1980
  - Daniel Yankelovich, Inc.
    - Advertisement: New York Times, undated (Box 61:1428)
    - Advertisement: The Yankelovich Report, undated (Box 61:1429)
    - "The Changing Nature of the Family", undated (Box 61:1430)
    - Description of services, 1968-1969 (Box 61:1431)
    - Memorandum concerning study findings on black urban life, 1967 Dec (Box 61:1432)
    - "The Public's Image of the Presidential Candidates", 1960 Feb (Box 61:1433-1434)
    - Voter telephone survey (wave III): statistics tables, 1972 (Box 61:1435-1437)
    - American Health article concerning Gallup survey on physical fitness, 1985 Mar (Box 61:1438)
    - Health management scale questionnaire, 1990 (Box 61:1439-1440)
    - D. Yankelovich correspondence and notes, 1990 (Box 61:1441)
    - Visual Aids
      - Ad effectiveness, undated (Box 61:1442)
      - Political, undated (Box 61:1443)
      - Ford, undated (Box 62:1444)
      - Ross Laboratories, undated (Box 62:1445)
      - Coty, undated (Box 62:1446)
      - Schlitz Beer, undated (Box 62:1447)
      - Sick's Ranier, undated (Box 62:1448)
      - Dow Chemical, 1963 (Box 62:1449)
  - Democratic Leadership Council (DLC)
    - Citizenship and National Service: A Blueprint for Civic Enterprise, 1988 (Box 62:1450)
    - The New Orleans Declaration: A Democratic Agenda for the 1990s, 1990 (Box 62:1451)
    - The New American Choice: Opportunity, Responsibility, Community (resolutions of 1991 DLC convention), 1991 (Box 62:11451)
    - The New Democrat, vol. 3, nos. 3-4, vol. 4, no. 1, 1991-1992 (Box 62:1452)
    - DLC focus groups, 1992 (Box 62:1453)
    - D. Yankelovich correspondence with DLC, 1992 (Box 62:1454)
    - Notes for D. Yankelovich speech before DLC, 1992 (Box 62:1455)
    - Materials from 1992 DLC conference, 1992 (Box 62:1456-1458)
  - Institute for Global Ethics
    - Update newsletters, News Flash newsletters, and correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 62:1459-1460)
  - International Council for Educational Development
    - Access, Systems, Youth and Employment, 1976 (Box 62:1461)
  - National Science Foundation Advisory Council
    - Council meetings,1984-1985 (Box 62:1462-1463)
    - Reports
      - "National Science Foundation Advisory Council Report on Science and the Public", 1985 Fall (Box 62:1464)
      - Piel, Gerald, "The Mission of the NSF: A Comment on the Pluralistic Model", 1985 Jul (Box 62:1465)
      - "Report of the Committee on NSF as Bridge", 1985 (Box 62:1466)
      - "Report of the Social Contract Study Team", 1985 Jul (Box 62:1467)
      - "Report of the Subcommittee on Communication of Key Science Indicators and Issues", 1985 Jun (Box 62:1468)
  - Nature Conservancy
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 62:1469)
  - New Framework Group
    - SEE: Boxes 23-25
  - Progressive Policy Institute
    - Policy Reports, nos. 1, 3, 5, 6, 8, 10, 12, 1989-1991 (Box 62:1470-1471)
      - Public Entrepreneurship Series, nos. 1, 2, 1990 (Box 62:1472)
      - "The Politics of Evasion: Democrats and the Presidency", 1989 Sep (Box 62:1473)
      - "Equality and the American Creed: Understanding the Affirmative Action Debate", 1991 Jun (Box 62:1473)
      - "National Service and Student Aid: Myth and Reality", 1989 Sep (Box 62:1474)
      - "Abstracts of Publications", 1992 Jan 1 (Box 62:1474)
  - Psychology Today magazine
    - Behavior Today newsletters, 1970 (Box 62:1475)
    - Behavior Today newsletters, 1970-1975 (Box 63:1476-1485)
    - Survey on public attitudes and behavior related to exercise, 1985 (Box 63:1486-1487)
    - Survey on changes in lifestyles and exercise, 1986 (Box 63:1488-1489)
    - Psychology Today subscriber survey, 1986 (Box 63:1490)
    - Survey of adults' behavior and attitudes related to diet and exercise, 1987 (Box 63:1491-1492)
    - Memoranda concerning marketing strategies, 1988 (Box 63:1493)
    - Yankelovich, D., and T. George Harris, "From Hedonism to Health," American Health, 1984 Mar/Apr (Box 63:1494)
    - Yankelovich, D., "Our Turn," American Health, 1988 Sep (Box 63:1494)
    - Transcript of Psychology Today staff meeting, 1988 Oct 17 (Box 63:1495)
    - Material concerning Psychology Today subscriber survey, 1988-1989 (Box 63:1496-1497)
    - Material concerning Psychology Today study on the driving experience, 1989 (Box 63:1498)
    - Edited articles, 1988-1989 (Box 64:1499-1503)
    - Correspondence (primarily with T. George Harris), 1988-1992 (Box 64:1504-1506)
    - Pyschology Today issues, 1989 Mar - 1990 Feb (Box 64:1507-1511)
  - Public Agenda Foundation
    - Corporate Affiliates Program, 1980 (Box 64:1512)
    - Executive summary of childcare project, 1982 (Box 64:1513)
    - Melville, Keith and John Doble, "Gauging the Public's Reaction to Reform of the Social Welfare System: Proposal for a National Citizen Review Panel", 1986 Dec (Box 64:1514)
    - Memoranda concerning future projects, undated, 1980 (Box 64:1515)
    - Nuclear arms and national security: survey data, 1982 (Box 64:1516)
    - Overview of project proposal concerning nuclear arms race, 1985 (Box 64:1517)
    - Overview of project proposal concerning nuclear arms race, 1983 (Box 64:1518)
    - Request for a planning grant to develop an alternative model for media-public communications, 1981 Mar (Box 64:1519)
    - Research proposal concerning an informed public - draft, 1982 Dec (Box 64:1520)
    - Seminar with Los Angeles Times, 19891 (Box 64:1521)
    - Reports
      - American's Talk Security - Citizen's Attitudes About National Security: A Report on a Series of Focus Groups (2 copies), 1987 Dec (Box 64:1522)
      - Assessing the Presidential Selection Process (2 copies), 1983 Nov (Box 65:1523-1524)
      - Childcare: Choices, 1981 (Box 65:1525)
      - Childcare: A Review of the Issue, [1981] (Box 65:1526-1528)
      - Childcare in the United States, [1983] (Box 65:1529-1533)
      - Childcare and Working Parents - draft, 1982 (Box 65:1534)
      - Childcare and Working Parents - executive summary, 1983 (Box 65:1535)
      - Crime and Corrections: The Public's View (2 copies), 1986 Sep (Box 65:1536-1537)
      - Crime and Correction: A Review of Public Opinion Data Since 1975 (2 copies), 1986 Sep (Box 65:1538-1539)
      - Crime and Punishment: The Public's View, 1987 Jun (Box 65:1540)
      - Crime and Punishment: The Public's View, 1991 feb (Box 65:1541)
      - Economic Policy and the Question of Political Will - draft, 1980 Feb (Box 66:1542)
      - Employment Security - draft, 1985 Sep (Box 66:1543)
      - Health Care Data and Issues Compendium - draft, 1993 (Box 66:1544-1552)
      - Health Vote: A Citizen Choice Campaign, 1983 (Box 66:1553)
      - Health Vote '82 - Curbing Health Care Costs: The Public's Prescription (2 copies), 1983 Apr (Box 66:1554-1555)
      - Industrial Policy: Help or Harm for the American Economy, 1984 Feb (Box 66:1556)
      - Inflation and the Presidency in the Nixon, Ford, Carter, and Reagan Administrations, 1983 Nov (Box 66:1557-1563)
      - The Kanawha Valley: A Report on Public Attitudes Toward Economic Benefits and Environmental Risks, 1986 Jan (Box 66:1564)
      - Older Americans and the Workplace - draft, [1983] (Box 67:1565-1571)
      - The Nation Reacts to AIDS: A Report from Six Cities (2 copies), 1988 Aug (Box 67:1572-1573)
      - Nuclear Proliferation: The Public's View, 1985 Aug (Box 67:1574)
      - People and New Technologies: An Issue for Managers (2 copies), 1983 Aug (Box 67:1575-1576)
      - Prison Overcrowding and Alternative Sentences: The Views of the People of Alabama, 1989 Feb (Box 67:1577)
      - Prison Overcrowding and Alternative Sentences: The Views of the People of Alabama - Technical Appendix, 1989 Feb (Box 67:1578)
      - Public Chemistry: A Report on the Feasibility of a Communications Project for the Kanawha Valley, 1985 Oct (Box 67:1579)
      - Public Choice Research: The Generation of Choices - draft, 1985 Jul (Box 67:1580)
      - The Public's Perspective on Social Welfare Reform (2 copies), 1988 Jan (Box 67:1581-1582)
      - Punishing Criminals: The Publics View; An Alabama Survey, 1989 (Box 68:1583)
      - Putting the Work Ethic To Work: A Public Agenda Report on Restoring America's Competitive Vitality, 1983 (Box 68:1584)
      - Saving: Good or Bad? A Pilot Study on Public Attitudes Toward Saving, Investment and Competitiveness, 1989 (Box 68:1585)
      - Science Policy Priorities and the Public, 1983 (Box 68:1586)
      - The Speaker and the Listener: A Public Perspective on Freedom of Expression (2 copies), 1980 (Box 68:1587-1588)
      - The Spread of Nuclear Weapons: The Public's View, 1986 (Box 68:1589)
      - Today's American Woman: How the Public Sees Her, 1980 Sep (Box 68:1590)
    - Press Releases
      - "Does the American Public Really Care About Education?", 1991 (Box 68:1591)
      - "Public Sees Mandatory Recycling as Best Approach to Garbage Problem", [1991] (Box 68:1591)
      - "Americans Will Sacrifice Many Things, But Not Their Cars, To Counter Threat of Global Warming", [1991] (Box 68:1591)
    - Domestic Policy Association, National Issues Forum, prepared by the Public Agenda Foundation
      - Pamphlet, undated (Box 68:1592)
      - Inflation, 1982 (Box 68:1593)
      - Jobs and Productivity, 1982 (Box 68:1594)
      - Retirement and Social Security, 1982 (Box 68:1595)
      - The Domestic Policy Association's National Issues Forum: A Report on Its First Year, [1983] (Box 68:1596)
      - Nuclear Arms and National Security, 1983 (Box 68:1597)
      - The Deficit and the Federal Budget, 1983 (Box 68:1598)
      - On Second Thought: Citizens and Leaders Address Three of the Nation's Pressing Issues, 1984 (Box 68:1599)
      - The Soviets: What Is the Conflict About?, 1985 (Box 68:1600)
      - Welfare: Who Should Be Entitled to Public Help?, 1985 (Box 68:1601)
      - On Second Thought 1986 - A Report on the 1985 Forums, 1986 (Box 68:1602)
      - Crime: What We Fear, What Can Be Done, 1986 (Box 69:1603)
      - Immigration: What We Promised, Where to Draw the Line, 1986 (Box 69:1604)
      - The Farm Crisis: Who's in Trouble, How to Respond, 1986 (Box 69:1605)
      - On Second Thought: A Report on the 1986-87 Forums, 1987 (Box 69:1606)
      - Freedom of Speech: Where to Draw the Line, 1987 (Box 69:1607)
      - The Superpowers: Nuclear Weapons and National Security, 1987 (Box 69:1608)
      - The Trade Gap: Regaining the Competitive Edge, 1987 (Box 69:1609)
      - A Report on the 1987 Forums, [1988] (Box 69:1610)
      - Coping with AIDS: The Public Response to the Epidemic, 1988 (Box 69:1611)
      - A Report on the 1988 Forums, 1989 (Box 69:1612)
      - The Day Care Dilemma: Who Should Be Responsible for the Children?, 1989 (Box 69:1613)
      - The Environment at Risk: Responding to Growing Dangers, 1989 (Box 69:1614)
      - The Drug Crisis: Public Strategies for Breaking the Habit, 1989 (Box 69:1615)
      - The Battle Over Abortion: Seeking Common Ground in a Divided Nation, 1990 (Box 69:1616)
      - Remedies for Racial Inequalities: Why Progress Has Stalled, What Should Be Done, 1990 (Box 69:1617)
      - "Issues Briefs" section for Reporter's Source Book, 1991 (Box 69:1618-1619)
      - America's Role in the World: New Risks, New Realities, 1991 (Box 69:1620)
      - Energy Options: A Report on the Outcomes of the National Issues Forums - draft, 1991 (Box 69:1621-1622)
      - The Boundaries of Free Speech: How Free Is Too Free?: A Report on the Outcomes of the National Issues Forums, 1992 (Box 69:1623)
      - Criminal Violence: What Direction Now for the War on Crime?, 1992 (Box 69:1624)
      - The Health Care Crisis: Containing Costs, Expanding Coverage, 1992 (Box 69:1625)
      - Energy Options: Finding Solutions to the Power Predicament, 1993 (Box 69:1626)
      - Prescription for Prosperity: Four Paths to Economic Renewal, 1993 (Box 69:1627)
  - TIME Magazine Consultant
    - Attitudes towards Gorbachev: memorandum, 1987 Dec 1 (Box 69:1628)
    - Duncan, Dick, 1986-1987 (Box 69:1629)
    - Press instrusiveness: data, 1987 Nov 16 (Box 70:1630)
    - Post-Reagan era: memorandum, 1987 Feb 15 (Box 70:1631)
    - "A Report on the Fortune 500/Yankelovich Survey," reprinted from September 1969 issue of Fortune, 1969 (Box 70:1632)
    - Material concerning offshoot of Coming to Public Judgment project, 1991 (Box 70:1633-1634)
    - Fortune Magazine (division of Time, Inc.) interview with D. Yankelovich, 1991 (Box 70:1635)
    - Fortune article concerning D. Yankelovich poll, 1991 Dec 2 (Box 70:1636)
    - Yankelovich, D., "The Seven Stages of Public Opinion," - draft for Fortune, 1992 Feb 10 (Box 70:1637)
  - William T. Grant Foundation Commission on Work, Family and Citizenship
    - William T. Grant Foundation Annual Report for FY 1985, 1986 (Box 70:1638)
    - Establishment of Commission, 1986 (Box 70:1639)
    - Mission statement, 1986 (Box 70:1640)
    - "A Brief Review of Previous Reports on Youth in America", 1986 (Box 70:1641)
    - "A Tentative Work Plan for the Commission", 1986 Dec (Box 70:1642)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 70:1643)
    - First Commission Meeting, 1987 Jan (Box 70:1644)
    - Third Commission Meeting, 1987 Sep 27-29 (Box 70:1645-1646)
    - Comments on draft of interim report for Third Meeting, 1987 Sep (Box 70:1647)
    - Fourth Commission Meeting, 1987 Dec 6-7 (Box 70:1648)
    - Incomplete draft of final Commission report, 1988 (Box 70:1649)
    - Material concerning release and marketing of final Commission report, 1988 (Box 70:1650-1651)
    - Material concerning release and marketing of final Commission report, 1988 (Box 71:1652)
    - Final Commission Report press conference, 1988 Nov (Box 71:1653)
    - Drafts on interim Commission Report on non-college youth, 1988 (Box 71:1654)
    - Reports